It was long.
長かったね
Wow!
わー!
beautiful!
綺麗!
first time!
初めて!
There's a lot of tension, after all.
テンションあるよね、やっぱりね
Look again.
また見て
You've arrived, you've arrived.
着いたね、着いたね
We've arrived.
着きましたよ
It smells like the sea.
海の匂いがする
I did it earlier.
さっきからしたけど
lie?
嘘?
Didn't you do it the moment you got off the train?
電車が降りた瞬間はしなかった?
I didn't.
しなかった
Does it smell delicious?
美味しい匂いか
The delicious smell of the sea.
海の幸な匂い
I'm hungry.
お腹減る
train.
電車
I'm going up.
上るよ
Let's do our best.
頑張ろう
Omikuji.
おみくじ
Which fortune?
どのおみくじ?
Is this it?
これか
Edoshima Shrine.
江戸島神社
How much does it cost?
いくら入るの?
100 yen.
100円
thank you.
ありがとう
I'm going.
行きます
Where shall we go?
どっから行こう?
Please separate it with your fingers.
手指で分けてください
this.
これ
Number 47.
47番
Does that mean 47 is good?
47はいいってこと?
low.
低い
I'm going.
行きます
what?
何?
Nakayoshi.
中吉
let's go.
行こう
Aim for Daikichi.
目指せ大吉
once again.
もう一度
Until I go.
行くまで
The place I passed by.
通ってきたところ
It's amazing to see it like this.
こうやって見るとすごいね
Looks like a toy.
おもちゃみたい
I'm against it.
反対だよ
This way?
こっちか
You might not see it that far.
そこまで見えないかも
You can't see it unless you put it somewhere else.
他に入れなきゃ見えない
It says 1.5 minutes.
1.5分間って書いてある
look?
見る?
1.5 minutes.
1.5分間
amazing.
すごい
It was so close that I could only see the roof.
近すぎて全然屋根しか見えない
picture?
え?
people.
人
I saw it.
見えた
i am here.
ここにいるよ
Now in the best position.
今ベストポジションに
What do you see?
何が見えるの?
Like the house in the back.
奥の家みたいな
Can you see it?
見えてるの?
I can see it.
見えてる
Lots of people.
人がいっぱい
thank you.
ありがとう
Ah, that dragon from earlier.
あ、さっきの竜
That's true.
本当だね
It smells good.
いい匂いする
I'm scared that it's going to snap off.
ポギっと折れそうで怖いんだけど
No matter what I think about it, I get angry.
どうしよう思ったら怒られる
I get angry.
怒られちゃう
Look again.
もう一回見て
reach.
届く
Just barely.
ギリギリ
It all hits me in the head.
全部頭に当たってるんだけど
If you come here, you'll win everything.
こっちに来たら全部当たる
Won?
当たる?
Yeah.
うん
Does it all hit your head?
頭に全部当たってる?
Everything is correct.
全部当たってる
I thought there was a row over there, and everyone got in the canoe.
あそこの一列何かと思ったら みんなカヌー乗ってやる
It's true.
本当だ
Looks like fun.
楽しそうだね
beautiful.
綺麗
Okay, let's go.
よし、行くぞ
Let's go.
行 くぞ
start.
スタート
I can't see it at all.
全然見えへん
It's a great salty smell.
すっごい潮の匂いですね
Which one am I?
僕すでさんどれや?
I don't know.
わかんない
There, there, there, there.
あそこ、ほらほらほら
I can see a white spot.
白いところが見える
I can't see it at all though.
全然見えてないけど
The mountains are a little whiter.
山ちょっと白くなってる
Ah, there, there, there, there.
あ そ こ、 ほらほらほら
Whale jawbone.
鯨のあごの骨
It looks like something like Totoro will appear.
なんかトトロとか出てきそう
Okay.
よし
Turn.
回します
It's written inside too.
中にも書いてる
Okay.
よし
Wow, it's really noisy.
うわ、めっちゃうるさいんだけど
Okay.
よし
I was tied.
結ばれちゃった
I'm writing that I don't have any luck.
もましらすありませんって書いてる
That's a shame.
残念ですね
Apparently not.
ないらしい
Everything looks delicious.
全部美味しそう
I want to eat it all.
全部食べたい
Can I eat it all?
全部食べていい?
Calemon, Calemon, Calemon.
カレモン、カレモン、カレモン
delicious.
美味しい
Puripuri.
プ リプリ
delicious.
美味しい
delicious?
美味しい?
delicious.
美味しい
Tea, this is good.
お茶、こっちがいい
what is this?
これは何?
Looks like a car.
車みたい
Tea like grandpa.
おじいちゃんみたいなお茶の
Because he's a grandpa.
お じいちゃんだから
Sour.
渋い
hot.
熱い
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
warm.
温かい
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
dazzling.
眩しい
You two came to this place.
このところに来ちゃったね、二人で
hey.
ね
Jump out.
飛び出して
it was fun.
楽しかった
It's really amazing.
め っちゃすごい
It's a little closer.
もうちょっと近いんですよ
still.
まだ
I'm going to do one more thing.
もう一件、行っちゃうからね
It's true.
ほんとやね
Can I go?
行ってもいいの?
It's here.
来ちゃった
It's coming, it's coming.
来ちゃった、来ちゃった
I'll do something wrong again.
またいけないことするね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you going to clap your hands?
手ぶたぶしちゃう?
I'm going to fall.
落ちちゃう
It's cute.
かわいいね
It's getting hot.
熱くなってる
Very naughty.
めちゃくちゃエッチ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I looked like an adult.
なんか大人の顔になってたよ
Sexy.
セクシーな
What do you want today?
どうしてほしい、今日は?
What do you want me to do?
何してほしい?
I want you to feel good.
気持ちよくしてほしい
Does it feel good?
気持ちよく?
Then take this off.
じゃあこれ脱いで
Panties.
パンティーを
Check that it is not tight.
締め付いてないとチェック
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Naughty.
エ ッチ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's a finger.
指だね
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
Look at your face.
顔見てよ
Are you sitting?
座りてる?
Riding.
乗ってて
Were you used to it?
なれてた?
I'm gone.
いっちゃった
Does this feel good?
この気持ちいい?
Can I show you?
見せていい?
Look behind you.
後ろ、あっち見て
I want you to come out.
出てきてほしい
You're sleeping amazingly.
すごい寝てるね
Look here.
こっち見て
Can I take it out?
出してもいい?
I'm sleeping a lot.
め ちゃめちゃ寝てる
Who is there?
誰がいる?
車
That's terrible.
やばいね
It's dangerous, it's dangerous.
やばいやばい
Can I run it?
流してもいい?
It's still flowing.
まだ流してる
How do I flush it?
どうやって流すの?
this.
これ
Do it.
やって
May I?
いいですか?
Does it feel good if I apply it lightly on the top?
上に小まかに当てたら気持ちいい?
Let's smoke each other's coffee.
カワーを吸い合って
It's like a bubble bath.
バブルバスみたいだね
yes.
そう
I suddenly feel hot.
急に熱い気がする
bubble bath.
バブルバス
how?
どうやって?
Like this.
こうやって
May I?
いいですか?
This also looks like Arcane.
これもアルカネみたい
I feel like an idiot.
バカみたい
May I?
いいですか?
What about now?
今、どうかな?
Don't you have a pen or something?
ペンとかつけないの?
pen.
ペン
Is it going up?
上がってる?
It's rising.
上がってる
good?
いい?
It went up.
上がった
Kuma-chan.
くまちゃん
hard.
大変
It's tough.
大変だ
What about on top?
上にどうとか
amazing.
すごい
Isn't it easy to touch your penis?
ちんこ触りやすくない?
It's true.
本当だ
Touch it.
触って
My daughter has a dick so I let her touch it.
娘のチンチンしてるから触らす
Itch.
イッチ
That's a pervert.
変態だね
He's a pervert.
変 態だ
Are you happy to be standing?
立って嬉しいでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
I'm glad to see you standing tall.
チンチン立って嬉しいって
Did you jerk off?
シコシコしたの?
Did you sneeze?
シ コシコしたの?
Did you jerk off?
シコシコしたの?
Could you please watch this?
これ見ててくれない?
Look at this.
これ見て
Shikoshikoshikoshiko.
シコシコシコシコ
Pen-chan.
ペンちゃん
Pen-chan?
ペンちゃん?
Pen-chan.
ペンちゃん
Stop it!
やめろよ
Raise it.
上げて
Are you taking it out?
抜いてるの?
I'm pulling it out.
抜いてる
I pulled it out earlier, but I wonder if it's pulled out?
さっきも抜いちゃったけど抜いてるかな?
It's removed.
抜いてるじゃん
I'm pulling it out.
抜いてます
Miss.
お嬢さん
Because I do naughty things.
イ ッチなことするから
If you do something naughty, young lady.
イッチなことしたらお嬢さん
different.
違う
I thought my teacher would make me stand up like this on the floor.
先生にフロアでこんなふうに立ちバックさせられると思ってな
Apparently it was.
かった らしい
I'll show you the corner.
コーナー見せちゃうね
Shall I show you the corner?
コーナー見せちゃう?
And it will attack you soon.
しかもすぐ襲うからしね
Can I still open it?
まだ開けちゃう?
I can't open it.
開けないよ
Both sides show the corner the most.
両辺が一番コーナー見せちゃう
Inside.
中の
all.
全部
Do you like standing back?
立ちバック好きなの?
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
Does it taste real?
本 人の味する?
delicious.
美味しい
Is it delicious?
美味しいの?
I didn't know before, which one is delicious?
さっきも知らずどっちが美味しい?
Which?
どっち
I'll continue if you ask me.
頼んだら続きしようか
It was up here.
こっちに上がってた
That's bad.
悪いね
Take a break.
休憩して
Since it's Morima, I'll hide.
森間だから隠れちゃう
When it comes, I'll hide.
来ると隠れちゃうね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
When I feel like I'm about to go, I say I'll go.
行きそうになったらちゃんと行くって言うんだよ
Is it skin flare?
肌肌フレアなの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I'm glad you worked hard.
一生懸命してくれて嬉しい
That's the position it was in.
そんな位置だったんだね
I'll continue if I want to include it.
入れたくなったらつづいてるよ
I want to go out.
出たい
Would you like to try it yourself?
自分で腰いってみる?
Very messed up.
すごくいじめちゃくちゃ
Look behind me.
後ろに見て
It felt good.
気持ちよかったね
Do you want to stay the night?
泊まってきたい?
I want to stay the night.
泊まりたい
Call your mom.
お母さんに電話して
It's true.
本当だ
Don't call.
電話しない
Call your mom.
お母さんに電話して
Because I won't be staying overnight.
泊まらないから
Say it's a friend's house.
友達の家とか言って